{"qid": "hard-agenda-0040", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Alice from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/06 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-1:00 PM, 3:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0041", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Victoria from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/08/05 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0042", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Faith from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/04/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0043", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Patrick from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/07/26 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0044", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Alice from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/03/09 in the agenda table?", "answer": "11:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0045", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Hector from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/12 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0046", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Georgina from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/03/20 in the agenda table?", "answer": "10:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0047", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Lily from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/02/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0048", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Joshua from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/12/02 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0049", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Madison from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/12/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0050", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with James from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/04/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0051", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Daisy from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/10/03 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-1:30 PM, 2:30 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0052", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Lucy from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/10/09 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-11:00 AM, 12:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0053", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Millie from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-10:00 AM, 1:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0054", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Layla from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/11/26 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 5:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0055", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Amelia from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/10/18 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-9:30 AM, 1:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0056", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Elizabeth from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-10:00 AM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0057", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Emma from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/06/14 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0058", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Hector from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0059", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Jessica from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/11/28 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:00 PM", "type": "schedule"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0060", "question": "What events does Brian have on 2022/03/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Art walk, Book signing", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0061", "question": "What events does Benjamin have on 2022/06/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": "fitness bootcamp", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0062", "question": "What events does James have on 2022/11/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Food Festival", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0063", "question": "What events does Amelia have on 2022/09/18 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Yoga and meditation", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0064", "question": "What events does Stephen have on 2022/05/22 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Employee team building event", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0065", "question": "What events does George have on 2022/07/03 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Art Auction", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0066", "question": "What events does Phoebe have on 2022/12/19 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Cheese + Wine festival", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0067", "question": "What events does Millie have on 2022/12/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Theatre play", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0068", "question": "What events does Andrew have on 2022/06/12 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Artisanal candy making class", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0069", "question": "What events does Jade have on 2022/01/25 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Kids concert", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0070", "question": "What events does Sophia have on 2022/03/28 in the agenda table?", "answer": "poetry reading event", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0071", "question": "What events does Elsie have on 2022/04/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Casino night", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0072", "question": "What events does Imogen have on 2022/02/04 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Food festival", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0073", "question": "What events does Lily have on 2022/04/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Dinner", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0074", "question": "What events does Daniel have on 2022/01/23 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Boxing class, Street art tour", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0075", "question": "What events does David have on 2022/05/28 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Art Exhibition", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0076", "question": "What events does James have on 2022/10/23 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Mindfulness meditation class", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0077", "question": "What events does Jasmine have on 2022/05/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Vegan Food Festival", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0078", "question": "What events does Summer have on 2022/04/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Book club meeting", "type": "all events"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0079", "question": "What events does Emily have on 2022/09/19 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Theatre performance, Art Walk", "type": "all events"}
